<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE channel [
  <!ENTITY lsquo "&#145;">
  <!ENTITY rsquo "&#146;">
  <!ENTITY ldquo "&#147;">
  <!ENTITY rdquo "&#148;">]>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Westhouse Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/westhouse-blog/</link>
    <description>A fantastic hotel</description>
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Experience the White Light Festival like a VIP</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/experience-the-white-light-festival-like-a-vip/</link>
        <description>For the seventh year in a row, Lincoln Center will play host to the White Light Festival from October 16 to November 16.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why We Love New York City in the Fall</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-in-the-fall-2016/</link>
        <description>The harvest season brings its own charms to the Big Apple. Here are a few reasons we love New York City in the fall.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Touring the Affordable Art Fair</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/affordable-art-fair/</link>
        <description>The Affordable Art Fair is in town, showcasing works from more than 1,000 artists at Chelsea&rsquo;s Metropolitan Pavilion.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Dine During New York Oyster Week</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/new-york-oyster-week/</link>
        <description>Oysters are served (especially raw) as a delicacy, and there’s no better time to sample the best in the city than during New York Oyster Week.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to See New York Fashion Week Like a VIP</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/vip-nyfw-new-york-fashion-week/</link>
        <description>How to see NYFW like a VIP.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Eat in NYC Now: Interview with Emily Elyse Miller of Trends on Trends</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/where-to-eat-nyc-interview-with-emily-elyse-miller-of-trends-on-trends/</link>
        <description>Everybody’s searching for the hottest restaurants and bars in New York. That’s why we sat down with Emily Elyse Miller—founder and creative director of Trends on Trends, a culinary trend forecasting agency, and curator of the WestHouse Dine Around guide—to find out where to eat and drink in New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Explore NYC on the East River Ferry</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/explore-nyc-brooklyn-east-river-ferry/</link>
        <description>A foodie-friendly guide to exploring New York via the East River Ferry.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The US Open: A VIP Guide</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/the-us-open-a-vip-guide/</link>
        <description>The best ways to see the US Open like an A-lister.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Perfect Day at the Jazz Age Lawn Party</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/jazz-age-lawn-party-nyc-governors-island/</link>
        <description>Here's what you need to know about NYC's Jazz Age Lawn Party on Governors Island.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Spend a Day in Lincoln Square</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/24-hours-nyc-lincoln-square/</link>
        <description>There’s more to Lincoln Square than its hallmark performing arts center.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WestHouse Guide to NYC Restaurant Week in Midtown</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-restaurant-week-guide/</link>
        <description>The list of restaurants participating in NYC Restaurant Week 2016 is up, and a slew of Midtown’s best spots are on it.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Celebrate Bastille Day in NYC</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/bastille-day-nyc/</link>
        <description>Bastille Day, also known as French National Day, celebrates the beginning of the French Revolution. Manhattan may be more than 3,600 miles from Paris, but Francophiles in New York have a wide choice of things to do to celebrate.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Rooftop Bars in NYC to Visit Now</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-rooftop-bars-restaurants/</link>
        <description>It’s time to head up to the best rooftop bars and restaurants in New York.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Celebrate the 4th of July in NYC</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/4th-of-july-things-to-do-nyc/</link>
        <description>Independence Day in New York City means the Macy’s 4th of July Fireworks.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WestHouse Guide to the Hamptons</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/westhouse-guide-to-the-hamptons/</link>
        <description>From 18th-century singled houses to estates hidden behind boxwood hedges, the Hamptons have long been a summer destination for NYC residents.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding the Hamptons in NYC</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/finding-the-hamptons-in-nyc/</link>
        <description>Approximately 100 miles east of Midtown Manhattan, The Hamptons are a string of seaside communities on Long Island’s South Fork. The 18th-century shingled houses and hidden estates behind boxwood hedges have long been a summer destination for NYC residents, but commuting several hours back and forth is a hassle, especially in summer traffic.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 NYC Parks Where You Can Dine Outside</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/5-nyc-parks-where-you-can-dine-outside/</link>
        <description>Summer is right around the corner, and New York isn’t waiting to get outside and enjoy the weather. From street cafes to rooftops, there’s no shortage of places to eat outside, but for a truly back-to-nature experience (at least in New York terms), you’ve got to eat in one of the city’s parks. Here are our favorite park restaurants.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WestHouse’s Guide to Biking the Hudson River Greenway</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/westgouses-guide-to-biking-the-hudson-river-greenway/</link>
        <description>No other bike route is as scenic as the Hudson River Greenway. Separated from motor traffic, the it’s the most popular bikeway in the United States. The bike and walking path runs 13 miles from northern Manhattan to the island’s southern tip, passing some of the city’s most famous attractions.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Art of Baking: Why You Need to Try Sweets by NYC’s Mini Melanie</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-desserts-mini-melanie/</link>
        <description>After working in the Michelin-starred kitchens at Babbo and Blue Hill, New York-based Melanie Moss opened Mini Melanie, selling nostalgic desserts with bold, artistic exteriors.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why You Need to Attend Frieze New York 2016</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/frieze-nyc-2016/</link>
        <description>Why Frieze New York is the art fair to see this spring</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NYC Attractions for Food Lovers: The WestHouse Insider’s Guide</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/where-to-eat-nyc-landmarks/</link>
        <description>New York City's top attractions and where to eat.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Find NYC&rsquo;s Most Famous Film Scenes</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-film-scene-locations/</link>
        <description>Movie locations offer a window into the past: from the glamor of the &rsquo;60s to the soul of the &rsquo;70s to the grit of the &rsquo;80s and beyond. While the landscape of the city changes on an almost daily basis, several film locations from the past 50 years still exist. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the New Met Breuer</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/met-breuer/</link>
        <description>The Metropolitan Museum has opened its second outpost: the modern and contemporary art branch now lives on the corner of Madison Avenue and 75th Street. Dubbed the Met Breuer, it&rsquo;s in the Whitney Museum&rsquo;s former building designed by architect Marcel Breuer.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Jacques Torres: King of the Chocolate Easter Bunny</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/jacques-torres-nyc-chocolate-easter-bunny/</link>
        <description>Master pastry chef Jacques Torres reveals five things we didn&rsquo;t know about his iconic chocolate Easter bunny.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to Do on a Rainy Day in NYC</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/56ed9ce4306c4f00032f4343/</link>
        <description>While a rainy day is never ideal, the city&rsquo;s best luxury shopping, acclaimed dining and noteworthy exhibitions can be enjoyed indoors.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four Meals from the Women Leading NYC&rsquo;s Restaurant Scene</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/women-leading-nyc-restaurant-scene/</link>
        <description>New York restaurants have long been known as macho places. But that&rsquo;s changing, thanks in no small part to the women chefs leading some of the city's best kitchens.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four Reasons Why NYC's Central Park is Best in Winter</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/central-park-winter/</link>
        <description>Most Central Park recommendations focus on summer activities, which makes sense, but this green space is actually even more fun in the winter. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which NYC Ice Skating Rink is Right for You?</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/ice-skating-nyc/</link>
        <description>The best ice skating rinks in New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five Reasons to Skip the Super Bowl this Weekend</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/super-bowl-2016/</link>
        <description>Five reasons to skip the Super Bowl and attend NYC's top attractions instead.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York City&rsquo;s New Valentine&rsquo;s Day Date Spots </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/new-valentines-day-date-spots-nyc/</link>
        <description>From skyscraper observation decks to underground parks, from world-class art to artisan cocktails, here are New York City&rsquo;s new date spots to visit this Valentine&rsquo;s Day.
</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding NOLA in NYC: Where to Celebrate Mardi Gras in New York City</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/mardi-gras-in-nyc/</link>
        <description>Where to celebrate Mardi Gras in New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where and What to Eat in NYC in 2016</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/where-to-eat-nyc-2016/</link>
        <description>The year 2016 has arrived, bringing New Year&rsquo;s resolutions with it. Read on for WestHouse&rsquo;s culinary take on the annual goals list.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to "Broadway Week 2016"</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/broadway-week-2016/</link>
        <description>For two weeks each winter, tickets to Broadway&rsquo;s top shows go on sale, as theaters hope to fill seats in New York&rsquo;s low season. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Hot Dogs in New York City</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-best-hot-dog/</link>
        <description>New York is world famous for its hot dogs. They're in almost every film, and they're on almost every block. While you can always stop at a Sabrett street cart (there are hundreds throughout Manhattan), we prefer these gourmet hot dog spots.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Year&rsquo;s Eve Champagne Countdown </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/new-years-eve-champagne-countdown/</link>
        <description>WestHouse&rsquo;s resident wine connoisseur Peter Ramondi shares his favorite bottles of bubbly to drink from early in the evening till the big moment at midnight.
</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WestHouse's Holiday Décor: The Inside Story</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/westhouse-holiday-decor/</link>
        <description>It&rsquo;s the holiday season in New York, and the entire city is getting into the spirit. From Rockefeller Center to the window displays of Fifth Avenue, Christmas decorations have transformed familiar attractions into winter wonderlands.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Christmas Window Displays in NYC</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-christmas-window-displays/</link>
        <description>The best holiday window displays in New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> Six NYC Holiday Traditions to Try This Year</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-holiday-traditions/</link>
        <description>New York City is one of America&rsquo;s best places to celebrate the holidays, with scores of attractions and traditions held throughout the month of December. Sometimes, however, the crowds, hassle or pure tackiness take away from the yuletide spirit. Here are three NYC alternate holiday traditions, along with three classics worth keeping.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best NYC Foods to bring to Thanksgiving Dinner</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-food-thanksgiving/</link>
        <description>New York City foods for Thanksgiving Dinner.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NYC Bars for Book Lovers</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-bars-for-book-lovers/</link>
        <description>Bars in Manhattan with a literary history, perfect for book lovers.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Buy NYC&rsquo;s Cutest Sweaters</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/where-to-buy-sweaters-nyc/</link>
        <description>Best Boutiques for Sweaters in New York City</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York City&rsquo;s Best New Year&rsquo;s Eve Parties</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-best-new-years-eve-parties/</link>
        <description>How to find the best New Year's Eve parties in New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trick-Or-Treating for Adults: NYC&rsquo;s Best Candy Shops</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-best-candy-shop/</link>
        <description>The best candy shops in New York City, just in time for Halloween.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best German, Austrian &amp;Swiss Restaurants in New York City</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-best-german-restaurants/</link>
        <description>The best German, Austrian and Swiss restaurants in New York City, including Manhattan and Brooklyn.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behind the WestHouse Fragrance</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/westhouse-fragrance/</link>
        <description>Luxury hotel with custom-designed scent.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to drink now</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/what-to-drink-now/</link>
        <description>The final weeks of summer are upon us, but we&rsquo;re holding on as long as we can, spending time on rooftops and at al fresco concerts—all of which, let&rsquo;s be honest, is an excuse to enjoy cold wine and beer. Peter Raimondi, Director of Food &amp;Beverage at WestHouse, reveals his picks for the best drinks of summer 2015.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Al Fresco Culture: The Best of New York&rsquo;s Outdoor Events</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/best-nyc-outdoor-events/</link>
        <description>New York City shines during the dog days of summer. Many locals are off vacationing, so there&rsquo;s a noted quiet in the normally clamorous streets. Come August, the cultural calendar starts picking up again, and everyone in the city spends as much time as possible attending outdoor events—this summer, Shakespeare has taken over, with three of his plays on park stages. Here&rsquo;s where to enjoy the best of Manhattan&rsquo;s al fresco culture:</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NYC Restaurant Week: Michelin Edition</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-restaurant-week-michelin/</link>
        <description>It&rsquo;s Restaurant Week in New York again. A true misnomer, the biannual celebration runs roughly a month long (until August 14), and invites diners to discounted, prix-fixe dinners and lunches at Manhattan&rsquo;s best restaurants. It&rsquo;s the perfect excuse to visit Michelin-starred restaurants at welcomingly low prices (lunches are $25; dinners $38).</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BROADWAY&rsquo;S BEST NEW SHOWS (&amp;WHERE TO EAT)</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/broadways-best-new-shows-where-to-eat-2/</link>
        <description>This summer, Broadway&rsquo;s most buzzed-about plays and musicals range from warm-hearted romances to darkly comedic puppet shows. But just because the shows themselves start at 8pm doesn&rsquo;t mean you need to wait till then to get into the dramatic spirit.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hotel Manager Bassim Ouachani on the WestHouse Experience</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/hotel-manager-bassim-ouachani-on-the-westhouse-experience/</link>
        <description>WestHouse Hotel  offers the ultimate luxury hospitality experience inviting leisure and business travelers alike to make WestHouse, Your house. At the helm, Hotel Manager Bassim Ouachani, ensures our residential-style hotel provides an unforgettable experience that is both one-of-a-kind and personal.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manhattan's best picnic spots</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/manhattans-best-picnic-spots/</link>
        <description>The sun is out, the rosé is chilled. It&rsquo;s the perfect time for a picnic in New York City. You might think that being a crowded island, Manhattan wouldn&rsquo;t have many options for a luxurious picnic. You&rsquo;d be wrong. Ask our WestHouse concierge to help set up a picnic delivery from some of New York&rsquo;s best restaurants or companies like Perfect Picnic and spend an afternoon at one of these beautiful spots right here in the concrete jungle.
</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New Whitney: What We've Learned</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/whitneymuseum/</link>
        <description>The Whitney Museum has been open in its new Meatpacking District location for a month now (about twenty minutes in a subway or cab away from WestHouse), and already it&rsquo;s an instant classic. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York&rsquo;s Best Steakhouses</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/new-yorks-best-steakhouses/</link>
        <description>If there&rsquo;s a better way to say &ldquo;Happy Father&rsquo;s Day&rdquo; than a big steak dinner, we haven&rsquo;t found it. After an elegant brunch at A Voce, part of our exclusive Father's Day package, you'll want to treat him to a special dinner. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York City's Best Rooftop Bar Views</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nycs-rooftop-bar-views/</link>
        <description>Ah, summer in the city. When the temperature rises, WestHouse Hotel guests start to drift toward the beautiful terrace on the 23rd floor, where there&rsquo;s cocktails, bar snacks and mind-blowing views of the city. It got us thinking...</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York City's Best Outdoor Workouts</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/nyc-outdoor-workouts/</link>
        <description>Warm weather has finally arrived here in the city, and the last place any of us want to be is inside the gym. Locals and visitors alike can agree that getting outside and exploring the city trumps sitting on the elliptical or lifting free weights in front of a mirror.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Children&rsquo;s Activities in New York City</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/best-childrens-activities-in-new-york-city/</link>
        <description>At WestHouse, kids (who we call &ldquo;Little Residents&rdquo;) can explore one of the world&rsquo;s most exciting cities just outside the hotel&rsquo;s front doors. We&rsquo;ve put together a list of the best activities, from famous toy stores and one-of-a-kind theatrical productions to secret Ninja restaurants and epic aerial tram rides.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Make A Stunning Flower Arrangement in 5 Easy Steps  </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/how-to-make-a-stunning-flower-arrangement-in-5-easy-steps/</link>
        <description>At WestHouse we are constantly inspired by the ever-changing blossoms in our lobby, and never more so than in the spring. Walk around the city and you&rsquo;ll see that every farmer&rsquo;s market, flower shop, and outdoor cafe is bursting with vibrant hydrangeas and blush-colored peonies. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Only-in-NYC Guide to Mother&rsquo;s Day</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/an-only-in-nyc-guide-to-mothers-day/</link>
        <description>From big parties on the sprawling New York Botanical Garden lawn to relaxing spa specials just for her, WestHouse can point you to the best Mother&rsquo;s Day celebrations in NYC. If you forgot a gift, no fear: WestHouse partner NET-A-Porter.Com has some suggestions.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Spin on an Old Fashioned </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/a-new-spin-on-an-old-fashioned/</link>
        <description>An Old Fashioned, which is whiskey or brandy muddled with sugar and bitters, topped with a twist of citrus, has taken on a distinctive new taste with the grand opening of The Den, WestHouse&rsquo;s speakeasy-inspired lounge.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Insider&rsquo;s Guide to the 2015 Frieze Art Fair </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/an-insiders-guide-to-the-2015-frieze-art-fair/</link>
        <description>WestHouse is proud to be an official hotel partner of Frieze New York, one of the world&rsquo;s leading contemporary art fairs. On May 14-17, Frieze New York will bring to Randall&rsquo;s Island Park more than 1,000 ground-breaking artists and 200 leading galleries from around the world. </description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WestHouse Itineraries: 5 Perfect NYC Excursions </title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/spring-2015-carnegie-hall-events/</link>
        <description>Carnegie Hall is woven tightly into the fabric of New York City, standing as a tradition-rich venue in the heart of Midtown Manhattan. But this classic venue isn&rsquo;t resting on its laurels.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Inspirational Designers</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/4-inspirational-designers/</link>
        <description>From the balcony of The Terrace at WestHouse Hotel, the heart of the city, the architectural grandeur of New York is breathtaking. At night, the light beaming from high-rise buildings illuminates the sky and magnifies the beauty of the city. Many designers and architects have left -- and will leave -- their personal imprint forever in the places and spaces that make up New York City.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bespoke Bath Products in NYC: The City&rsquo;s Top 6 Apothecaries</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/bespoke-bath-products-in-nyc-the-citys-top-apothecaries/</link>
        <description>Shop the best apothecaries and skin care shops in NYC to find the soothing solutions life in the big city requires.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New York City&rsquo;s Best Day Trips</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/new-york-citys-best-day-trips/</link>
        <description>The best day trips in New York City, all accessible from Manhattan by train or car.</description>        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Parks where you can dine outside</title>
        <link>http://www.westhousehotelnewyork.com/blog/parks-where-you-can-dine-outside/</link>
        <description>Summer is right around the corner, and New York isn’t waiting to get outside and enjoy the weather. From street cafes to rooftops, there’s no shortage of places to eat outside, but for a truly back-to-nature experience (at least in New York terms), you’ve got to eat in one of the city’s parks. Here are our favorite park restaurants.</description>        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>